

CONTACT



+49 1747827269



iomaroliverreyes@gmail.com



Erlangen, Langfeldstr 35, DE



linkedin.com/in/jdreyes24

SKILLS

Software & Hardware Installation

Troubleshooting & Maintenance

Cloud Computing & Virtualization

Microsoft Office & Adobe Apps

System & Network Administration



Web Design & Development

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - - -

ARABIC - -

GERMAN - - -

HOBBIES









JOMAR OLIVER REYES

I'm an experienced IT person who is passionate about technical support, maintenance, administration, and management that has a strong background in these aspects. A self-motivated and self-taught learner with a few experiences in web designing and development.

EDUCATION

BS in Information Technology

2017-2022

AMA University and Colleges

Major in Software Engineering and Web Application Development

Associate Degree in Computer Technology 2005-2007

Asian Institute of Computer Studies

Major in Computer Programming, Systems and Network Management

EXPERIENCE

IT - Systems Engineer

2018-2020

Velocity Solutions, Inc. (MSP) - Philippines & Hong Kong

Responsible for assisting/resolving the clients' requests & issues on Windows/Mac/Linux desktops, laptops, and servers thru remote and virtual environments. Setup, implement, manage and monitor IT Systems & Infrastructure.

IT - Support Specialist

2013-2017

Wallan Trading Co. & GAMA/KAMCJ – Saudi Arabia

Responsible for providing L1/L2 technical support via telephone, email, tickets, and remote desktop. Deploying, configuring, managing, maintaining, and monitoring the IT systems and network infrastructure of a contractual company and for the hospital as their client and providing a daily technical support and assistance routine.

IT - System & Network Administrator

2012-2013

Torch Film Productions Studios, Inc. - Philippines

Responsible for day-to-day operations and administration of IT Infrastructure. Securing the systems, business applications, and maintaining network stability.

IT - Support Engineer

2007-2012

Imaginary Friends Studio, Inc. - Philippines

Responsible for providing technical support to the users. Setup, configure new machines and maintain IT Systems, Network Infrastructure, and provide hands-on training for the users.